Guide to the George W. Perkins papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Financial Files, 1922-1937
  - Knauth, Nachod and Kuhne
    - Supreme Court--Charles S. Martin against William C. Peyton, George W. Perkins, Jr., Anne du Pont Peyton, Evelina B. Perkins, Dorothy Perkins Freeman and Edward W. Freeman, undated. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Stocks, 1925-1937 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Series V: Printed Material, 1909-1990_
  The pamphlets and brochures in this series are connected to Perkins’s main interests: foreign policy and service as well as parks and parkways. Also included are pamphlets from Robert College, Istanbul, for which Perkins served as a trustee from 1922 to 1960.
  - L’Atlantique Nord volume 4--With Article by George W. Perkins, Jr., 1957 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - "Decision on the Hudson," 1965 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Policy--Brochures, 1951-1952 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Service--Brochures, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - "Lighting the New York World’s Fair," 1940 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - "Merck," Fortune, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Merck and Co., Inc.--Pamphlets, 1942-1959 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - NATO
    - Brochures, 1949-1964, (4 Folders) (Box 43, Folder 1 to 4)
    - Commemorative US Postage Stamp, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - NATO, the First Five Years, 1949-19509 54--With Inscription and Note to George W. Perkins, Jr. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - New York State Parks, 1919-1954 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Palisades Interstate Park
    - Annual Reports, 1936-1938, 1961, 1969, (2 Folders) (Box 50, Folder 11 to 12)
    - Brochures and Maps, 1909-1960 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Brochures and Maps, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Nature Notes, 1933 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Parkway, 1953-1958 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Parkways, 1936-1954 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Paskell, Thomas--Pennsilvania 1683 a Page of Finnish History 1951 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Program for Extension of Parks and Parkways in the Metropolitan Region, 1930 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Report of the Postmaster General, 1921-1922, (2 Folders) (Box 44, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Robert College
      - Pamphlets, 1928-1957 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Reports and Speeches, 1909-1956 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Rosengarten, Frederic, Jr.--History of the Cinchona Project of Merck & Co Inc. and Experimental Plantations Inc, 1934-1943 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - State of New York Conservation Department--A Biological Survey of the Lower Hudson Watershed, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Voyage de M. le Président de la République et de Madame Vincent Auriol aux États-Unis d’Amérique et au Canada, 1951 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Series VI: Photographs, 1895-1970
  The bulk of this series consists of photograph albums from the 1910s through the 1930s, with pictures of travels to Alaska, Allagash, Central and South America, and Europe. There are also family portraits dating back to 1895 and official NATO photographs. This series includes negatives of photographs taken at Hill School from 1910 to 1913 and glass negatives of the family’s trip to Alaska in 1909. Of particular interests are photographs taken during a trip to India for the Chemical Warfare Service during World War II and an album with photographs from World War I.
  - Bridge, 1923-1924 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Buildings, undated (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Chemical Warfare Service--Brunskill Mission--India, 1944-1945 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Cunard White Star Liner, 1950s (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Department of State, 1950s, (2 Folders) (Box 45, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Guatemala, 1942, (2 Folders) (Box 45, Folder 8 to 9)
  - Hill School, 1910-1913, (4 Folders) (Box 51, Folder 6 to 9)
  - Hunter Club Dinner--The Hague, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Java, 1935 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Central and South America, 1922, (3 Folders) (Box 46, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Merck & Co--Board of Directors, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - NATO
    - General, 1955-1957, (4 Folders) (Box 46, Folder 5 to 8)
    - Supreme Allied Commander Atlantic Visit, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Negatives--Alaska, 1909 (Box 55)
  - Negatives--Hill School, 1910-1913, (2 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 10 to 11)
  - Palisades Interstate Parkway, 1958 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Photo Albums
    - 71st Regiment, World War I, circa 1916 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Alaska, 1909, (4 Folders) (Box 52, Folder 3 to 6)
    - Allagash, 1915 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Central and South America, 1935 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Sea Island, 1970 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - St. Helena, 1910s (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - South America--Honeymoon, 1922 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Wave Hill and European Trip, 1910s (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Wedding and Honeymoon, 1917 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Portraits
    - Family, 1895-1958, (2 Folders) (Box 47, Folder 1 to 2)
    - George W. Perkins, Jr., 1895-1959, (3 Folders) (Box 47, Folder 3 to 6)
    - George W. Perkins, Jr., 1910s (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - George W. Perkins, Jr., undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Katherine Trowbridge, 1910s (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Official, 1920s-1950s, (2 Folders) (Box 55, Folder 6 to 7)
  - Rockland Lake North--Opening Ceremonies, 1965 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Rome, 1930s (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Sea Island, undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Tallyrand, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Travel, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - United States European Command, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - World War I, circa 1916 (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Series VII: Other Media, 1940-1961
  This series includes records of speeches given at the General Ridgway Testimonial Dinner and at ceremonies held by the Palisades Interstate Park Commission. There is also a recording of a Christmas message to Austria delivered by Perkins while he was working for NATO.
  - Christmas Message to Austria by George W. Perkins, Jr., 1950 (2 records) (Box 51, Folder 12 to 13)
  - General Ridgway Testimonial Dinner, undated (5 records) (Box 51, Folder 14 to 18)
  - PIPC
    - Bear Mountain Bridge Ceremonies, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - George W. Perkins, Jr. Plaque Dedication, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 20)